ELIZABETH SUBHIKSHA VICTORIA

DESIGNER | DEVELOPER

+91 861 029 8756 elizabethsubhikshavictoria.23it@licet.ac.in

PROFILE

A highly charismatic and focus-driven technologist, who has a passion for web development and management, and an expert in channelizing my skills to ensure professional and personal growth, while contributing to the vision of the organisation.

EDUCATION

Loyola ICAM College of Engineering and Technology, Chennai B.Tech Information Technology 2019 - 2023

Good Shepherd Mat. Hr. Sec School, Chennai **HSC / SSLC** JUNE 2005 - APRIL 2019 Member of NCC, Sampoorna(NGO), School Band.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL:

Web Developer, IOT, Photoshop, Illustrator, Adobe XD, Content Writer

NON - TECHNICAL:

Interpersonal Communication, Public Relations, Adaptability, Teamwork, Content Creation, Decision Making, Leadership, Administration, Creative Thinking.

EXPERIENCE

LICET PATTARAI:

PRESIDENT - Pattarai, LICET (December 4 2021 - Present)

I ensure the club follows its objectives, mission, vision and procedures that are in place, and set policies and strategic direction for the community, for the near term and for the foreseeable future.

DIRECTOR OF ACTIVITIES - Pattarai, LICET (March 5 2021 - Present)

I collaborate and work with the upskilling and learning activities in our club, organizing events, workshops and coordinating with external colleges.

MENTORSHIP COORDINATOR - Pattarai, LICET (November 17 2020 - 5 March 2020)

I act as a coordinator for the freshers in our club for the mentorship programme.

PROJECT MANAGER - Pattarai, LICET (July 3 2020 - October 18 2020)

I coordinate people and ensure that our projects are delivered on time including planning, executing, evaluating and progressing accordingly.

HUMAN RESOURCE EXECUTIVE - Pattarai, LICET (21 July 2020 - 5 March 2020)

I learnt to stand as a channel of communication between various departments trying to manage and handle grievances, resolving issues, hiring and mentoring students.

FABLAB:

Event Facilitator - FABLAB, LICET (16 June 2021 - Present)

I ensure that the event's objectives are met effectively, with clear thinking and good participation.

COMPUTER SOCIETY OF INDIA:

TREASURER - CSI, LICET (6 October 2021 - Present)

I have been a part in coordinating and organizing an event.

ROTARACT:

INTERNATIONAL SERVICE DIRECTOR - Rotaract Club Of LICET, LICET (January 12 2022 - Present) I serve as the ISD of the Rotaract Club of LICET and help in bringing international projects and exposure to the club.

JOINT SECRETARY - Rotaract Club Of LICET, LICET (July 30 2020-Januray 11 2022)

I serve as the Joint Secretary of the Rotaract Club of LICET and help in bringing projects to the club, organizing events and maintaining the constitution of our club and it's records.

GSC:

SCHOOL CAPTAIN - Good Shepherd Matriculation Hr. Sec School (2015-2018)

I served as a House Captain for 3 consecutive years and managed all my work demonstrating leadership skills.

PROJECTS

Patient Tracking System (September 2021)

A simple Dental Specific for aligners & PSI Simulations Website using HTML, CSS, and JS with Flask Backend and Mysql DB.

• Kankanipalan (21 May 2021 - Present)

Kankaanipalan is an AI based monitoring system for rural and urban areas where stagnation of water, sewage are identified using the drone with machine learning modules.

CORTEX (2 December 2020 - Present)

An ERP suite for the club

• Project Caliditas - Smart Thermometer (July 3 2020 - March 28 2021)

Project Caliditas is a contactless thermometer that detects & records temperatures in an ERP database and raises the needed alerts if the temperature crosses the fever threshold.

• Website for the Rotaract Club of LICET (15 Jan - 9 March 2021)

Designed website for the Rotaract Club Of LICET using Bootstrap.

INTERNSHIPS

ARTCIC COOL ENGINEERS

Job: Web Developer

Duration: 2 July 2021 - 30 September 2021

MAKERSPACE

Job: IoT Engineer

Duration: 22 March 2021 - 5 April 2021

ICONIC DREAM PVT Ltd

Job: Front End Developer

Duration: 01 November 2021 - On going

• DOVE EVENTS PLANNERS

Job: Web Developer

Duration: January 2021 to February 2021

KATHIR KREATIONS

Job: MANAGEMENT INTERN

Duration: 15 January 2021 - 16 March 2021

PAPERS

• Secured second place in Paper Presentation about Nanophotonics at Shri Sai Ram Engineering College (March 14th 2020)

COMPETITIONS

- PALS NexGen 3D Hackathon Finalists (2 September 2021 9 September 2021)
- Top 10 finalists | Hackathon Aerotricz Competition (8 August 2021 to 15 August 2021)
- Secured second place in De Code De Veganza -FestX (14 June 2021)
- Ideathon top 10 organized by Pattarai (June 14 2020)
- Shortlisted for Smart India Hackathon 2020 Internal (27 Jan 2020)
- Won the 2nd prize in LICET INNOVATION CONTEST 2020 for First Years (6 November 2019)

ACTIVITIES

- Hosted several events as an MC
- Done a podcast and a part of a Podcast team TeaKadaiTalks
- Organized events as a part of Rotaract and Pattarai
- Worked as a member in the Public Relations Team for Josh Talks (12 & 13 October 2019)

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Oratory
- Debates
- VJ, MC
- Dancing
- Community Service

LANGUANGES

Tamil • • • •

English